[Music]
gluto Pia is that special place you've
always dreamed of but never knew existed
are 100% gluten-free artisan bakery here
we lovingly hand bake cakes brownies and
muffins everything is baked using the
best ingredients and always from scratch
we also serve gluten-free and vegan
breakfast and lunch as well as our
expanding range of freshly baked bread
since we launched flu topia the response
has been incredible in light of our
success and our passion for honest and
authentic baking we want to take the
next step and open our second gluto PA
storm in one of the largest markets of
all central London and this is where you
the investor come in to achieve our goal
we need your investment this money will
help us fit our or secondly topia store
in our next choice location the heart of
Soho so why does glute API link good
business sense in the UK the gluten-free
market is on the cusp of an explosion it
was valued at four hundred and seventy
million pounds in 2015 and reached over
half a billion at the end of 2016 and
it's forecast to grow by a further
thirty-five percent by 2020
[Music]
utopia is perfectly poised to tap into
this ever expanding market and the Soho
Bakery is just the beginning we're
targeting one newly topia store a year
for the next five years generating a
turnover in the region of three and a
half million pounds our intention is to
be the market leader as the gluten-free
revolution takes pace and your
investment can make this a reality join
us now on our journey and be an integral
part of the next big thing to hit the
baking industry utopia
you